Ilir Perolli

Nationality: Kosovar

**** (+383) 44547565

Date of birth: 20/07/1999

Gender: Male

™ Email address: ilir_perolli@live.com

Website: <u>amici.epizy.com</u>

Website: <u>bufi.epizy.com</u>

Website: <u>uniworks.epizy.com</u>

9 Github: : https://github.com/llirPerolli

Address: 9 Nentori nr.11, 50000 Gjakove (Kosovo)

ABOUT ME

Innovative web developer with 5 years of experience in the front-end and 3 years in the backend with PHP language. 1 year of experience with Data Science using Python. General knowledge in technologies such as: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, Object Oriented PHP, Laravel, JAVA, Python, Bootstrap, SQL, MySQL. Talented in project management, team leadership and independent problem solving.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Bachelor

Public University of Prizren "Ukshin Hoti" [01/10/2017 - 17/09/2020]

Address: Rruga e Shkronjave, 20000 Prizren (Kosovo)

uni-prizren.com

Master

Public University of Prizren "Ukshin Hoti" [01/11/2020 - Current]

Address: Rruga e Shkronjave, 20000 Prizren (Kosovo)

uni-prizren.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Instructor

Digital School [03/11/2020 - 30/06/2021]

City: Gjakove **Country:** Kosovo

Programming instructor (Html, CSS, Javascript, PHP and MySQL, Wordpress) for age groups from 16 to 18 years old and (Code, Scratch, App Inventor) instructor for age groups from 7 to 15 years old.

Web programmer

EGED (Entrepreneurship, Growth and Economic Development) - NGO [01/07/2019 - 10/01/2020]

City: Gjakove **Country:** Kosovo

Development and management of EGED websites and social networks, planning and designing projects related to programming and website development.

PROJECTS

Amici

Amici is a platform that enables users (mostly students) to access books and lectures making it easier for them to attend computer science classes. Literature in Amici account is divided based on the academic year in which the student is. Students can also exchange files (seminar papers, projects, photographs, etc.) of various kinds. Another option is to post the videos via the link, where the student first creates a folder by naming it (eg: "Lessons from Java") and then adds the videos to the folder by naming them first and placing the link. Among other things, students can communicate with each other through messages (chat), where they can discuss various topics or post a picture.

amici.epizy.com

Bufi

Bufi enables users (simple user or company) to post products or offer services on the web application. The post gives the name and description of the product as well as its price. Finally select the category, city and upload the photos for that product. Those products can then be viewed by other users, searched and users can follow each other in order for their posts to appear on the front page, without losing any product. The profiles of each business or ordinary user can also be viewed, with the possibility for another user to see all the products.

bufi.epizy.com

OpenBci controlling Dobot

OpenBCI stands for open-source brain-computer interface (BCI). In this project the electrical activity of body is sampled. The versatile and affordable biosensing systems are being used to sample electrical brain activity (EEG) to being able to more the robot called Dobot. The direction of Dobot is changed by blinking the eyes and the move is realized by concentrating and converting all the electrical brain activity in coordinates for Dobot.

https://github.com/llirPerolli/OpenBCI/tree/master/OpenBCI Tutorials-master/EMG Controlled Dobot

News Detector

In this project is made a simple news detector using Naive Bayes algorithm, which is a machine learning model that are a family of simple "probabilistic classifiers" based on applying Bayes' theorem with strong independence assumptions between the features. This classifier can detect news from different categories such as: sports, politics, health and economics.

https://github.com/llirPerolli/DataScienceProjects/tree/master/NaiveBayesNewsDetector

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s):

Albanian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

HTML / CSS / Bootstrap / PHP / SQL / MySQL / Java / Laravel / Javascript / Python

HONOURS AND AWARDS

First Place in Open ICT education for youth employment

Open Data Kosovo [27/01/2020]

Open ICT education for youth employment

PHP with Laravel

Udemy [05/09/2020]

PHP with Laravel for beginners - Become a master in laravel

Javascript & jQuery

Udemy [22/10/2020]

Javascript & jQuery - Certification Course for Beginners

Techstitution 4.0

Open Data Kosovo [11/11/2020]

Techstitution 4.0 Certificate of training